<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Temporary lights in place for NO apparent reason, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185726</link>
<description>Junction of Cirencester Road and Bafford Approach. I presume the Cirencester to Gloucester road may be shut again this evening and the London road in Charlton Kings may be shut again this evening and the temporary lights on the Cirencester Road have been left in place but there is NO obstruction in the road and there is a long tailback! Can we shut or cause unnecessary delays on any more roads to the south of Cheltenham at the same time?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Bafford Approach, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185726&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Information board identifying emergency contact company/number not displayed</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185726</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878336 -2.054677</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous complicated junction layout, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185642</link>
<description>Junction with Vale Road and Mirabelle Road is dangerous. I drove across from Mirabelle Road this afternoon, two cars approaching from Gotherington drove straight across in front of me, across my right of way. I had to stop to avoid collisions. You need to change this junction before an accident happens Turning right from Vale Road has poor visibility from the left because bushes have been left there, obscuring view of approaching traffic The Road sign (approaching from Station Road) shows you have priority but there is a give way sign there and priority is on Mirabelle Road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 22, Sharing Grove, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185642&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185642</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.954432 -2.055182</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Workers have left heavy machinery blocking public footpath, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185483</link>
<description>The public footpath of mead road found here https://maps.app.goo.gl/YAM8zFo5XCaUQFnu9 Has been blocked by heavy machinery making it almost impossible to use what is a busy footpath.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5185483.0.jpeg?0553fad8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Mead Road, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185483&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185483</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882759 -2.074248</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unauthorised parking restrictions, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185466</link>
<description>There is on road parking (i.e. slightly wider road) outside the small parade of shops on Blacksmith Lane. There is a standard blue and white parking time restriction sign and there is zero evidence that the parking is private land.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The newsagent is displaying prominent &amp;quot;warning&amp;quot; signs in his window that the &amp;quot;parking is only for customers&amp;quot; and that he has CCTV watching them.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I believe that this is an illegal attempt to apply parking restrictions to a public highway and threaten the public through the &amp;quot;warning&amp;quot; written in his signs and the threat of CCTV being used.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 4, Blacksmith Lane, Churchdown, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185466&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185466</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.876434 -2.167347</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185276</link>
<description>Inspect tree outside properties for Candice Bennings inc photos.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185276&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185276</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889444 -2.096509</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork problem, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185275</link>
<description>FMS 06/11/2023 - Storm drains in cul-de-sac adjacent to 27,29 Binyon Road causing huge lake of water. Need stormdrain cleaning .&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185275&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185275</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.953817 -1.971319</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bollards, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185091</link>
<description>Bollards that appear to have been installed to prevent pavement parking/driving for motor vehicles near the flats have made the cycle path more dangerous and almost unusable. The pathway is already very narrow and putting bollards either side is an accident waiting to happen. Its too narrow for cyclists to pass each other when going in opposite directions! Please correct.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 321, Princess Elizabeth Way, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185091&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5185091</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907929 -2.112121</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The boundary wall section on Thirlestaine Road entrance to Thirlestaine park residential development is showing serious signs of erosion which we believe is being caused by water on the highway. What could possibly be in the Road treatment that is causing this damage?, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184749</link>
<description>Section of boundary wall on Thirlestaine road adjacent to the Thirlestaine park entrance.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5184749.0.jpeg?c26b5711&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Waterfield Close, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184749&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184749</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889097 -2.071319</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bin full again, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184346</link>
<description>Bin by entrance to Burrows Field full again. Ubico were here yesterday. Please could these bins be made bigger or emptied more regularly? We shouldn&amp;#39;t have to keep on requi this. Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5184346.0.jpeg?e66e9953&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 107, Church Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184346&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184346</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875706 -2.082252</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The island is almost impossible to see at night. The white lines have faded away. There is no bollard. Insufficient lighting. This has cost us nearly £1000 in damage, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184314</link>
<description>This is very dangerous particularly at night and and when it is raining. No clear marking. No bollards etc. No lighting.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5184314.0.jpeg?ca77977f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A417, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184314&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184314</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.867497 -2.196521</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pallet full of plastic and dead fireworks dumped on pavement outside playgroup., 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184282</link>
<description>On the pavement outside PATA playgroup in Back Lane, Winchcombe.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5184282.0.jpeg?12c36f41&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Back Lane, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184282&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184282</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.953257 -1.970855</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>New fence is on lane not owned by home owner but on lane., 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184137</link>
<description>Spring Lane GL523PY House has erected fence onto lane past property wall/boundary. The landgrab has damaged high fibre internet cable buried there by gigaclear. They have cut two trees that were there, again on lane not their land, and planted new ones. All of this done in last three weeks. The cable will have to be relaid where cars park alongside the fence. Gigaclear asked who owned the land I said highways to best of my knowledge they said to call it in. Obviously they had permission to lay this.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5184137.0.jpeg?1b06c927&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Spring Lane, Southam, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184137&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5184137</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.937686 -2.02922</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Series of potholes opening up as road surface breaks up, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183953</link>
<description>On a section of Everest Rd between Southfield Close and Southfield Rise. Same problem happened last winter, was repaired but not very well as it’s happening sgain&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 27, Everest Road, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183953&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183953</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.87718 -2.068991</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>More potholes further down than the officer can acknowledge, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183774</link>
<description>Hello I have just had a chat with the officer marking the potholes in our lane , a very nice chap by the way, and he told me to contact yourselves because he is only allowed to mark the ones from the top of the lane down to Ruddles farm, but we have many many more further down the lane and some very wide and deepso can you please activate this and carry on down to gotherington fields farm and down to springfield hopefully then they could all be sorted. Lots of people are experiencing big problems here with these. Many thanks Alan Vine.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gotherington Fields, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183774&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183774</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964635 -2.083096</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hole in footway, can see water running underneath like a river when it rains, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183576</link>
<description>Hole in f/way outside driveway of 19 Gretton Road, GL52 9EP&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19, Gretton Road, Gotherington, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183576&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183576</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 10:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964445 -2.051198</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sign very faded, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183372</link>
<description>There&amp;#39;s a large sign shortly before the 300 yard marker before the J11 exit heading northbound on the M5. I believe it would have once been a brown sign advertising Regency Cheltenham, Gloucester Cathedral &amp;amp; Historic Docks and Forest of Dean, but is now light blue and quite difficult to read. Could this please be replaced - I&amp;#39;m not sure how long it has been like that for but it looks as though it has been a long time.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): M5, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183372&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damage to Sign (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183372</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881437 -2.151224</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183287</link>
<description>CBC requests a crown lift of a London plane tree adjacent to the war memorial. &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183287&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183287</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 09:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898996 -2.077461</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tarmac coming up on pavement causing holes to appear. Weeds have been cleared but this has resulted in tarmac coming up and spreading across the pavement and holes forming which could cause another accident. Neighbour has recently had a fall caused by this., 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183250</link>
<description>The pavement outside 2 Pembroke road gradually spreading across the pavement. This has been a problem for at least 10 years but as the problem is now spreading it could be a trip hazard to pedestrians, especially during dark evenings.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Pembroke Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183250&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183250</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 09:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885905 -2.116809</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Your Report says they&#39;ve been fixed... They haven&#39;t!, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5182901</link>
<description>10 metres of deep potholes many of which are deeper than a tennis ball&amp;#10;&amp;#10;They are sharp and have damaged our tyres and wheel rims due to their size&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5182901.0.jpeg?5f886781&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sevenhampton, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5182901&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5182901</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901895 -2.00551</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 7th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183100</link>
<description>email rcvd 06.11.23 - Good Morning &amp;#10;I would like to claim for a blow out that I had due to the poor condition of one of Tewkesbury B.C roads. On Friday the 6th of October I hit a massive pothole on the Gotherington Fields Road just off the A435, the pothole was just near the Ruddles farm stables, although the whole of that stretch of road is riddled with massive potholes and in terrible condition on the edges. This made me late for work as I had to do the spare and cost me £73.24. So, I would like to claim for the tyre and loss of earnings for that morning. If you need anything else, please let me know. All pictures attached , please see the damage the pothole done, it needs addressing asap as that stretch of the road is dreadful. &amp;#10;&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183100&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5183100</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964411 -2.081888</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>