<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Abandon trailer ouside flats .meaning vehicles park on grass verges opposite . damage to verge mud on path. slip hazard to elderly residents, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883258</link>
<description>On the road outsite flats 33-43 newton road.has been abandon for months. takes up parking space vehicle now park on grass verge opposit all along the road .deep ruts in grass , mud on path .slip hazard to elderly residents in the area&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 34, Newton Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883258&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883258</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904449 -2.111496</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic lights facing wrong way Albion Street, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883004</link>
<description>Traffic lights at crossing near shops on Albion Street are facing the wrong way&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 121;123, Albion Street, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883004&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Traffic light head is facing wrong direction</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883004</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898759 -2.068634</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Burnt out car, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883003</link>
<description>At the rear of 20 Ennerdale Road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19b, Ennerdale Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883003&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6883003</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888031 -2.112951</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>&#39;Parton Road&#39; street sign has been completely smashed and damaged by a recent car accident, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882824</link>
<description>Opposite community centre at the junction of mini roundabout.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Parton Road, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882824&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street nameplates</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882824</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883394 -2.170703</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unclear signage for temporary roundabout, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882532</link>
<description>I have had multiple occasions where traffic coming from Escourt Road direction towards the A40 has not stopped at the temporary roundabout whilst I have been traversing around the roundabout towards Church Road. The temporary traffic lights for the pedestrian crossings are confusing drivers in my opinion as they believe the lights are green for them to continue onwards. This is dangerous and someone will be hurt soon. This has been happening since the change from 3 way traffic control via temporary lights to this new layout with the roundabout.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road, Longlevens, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882532&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882532</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875249 -2.207244</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>300mm x 400mm x70 deep hole, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882473</link>
<description>This pothole is near the left hand corner of Severn Road where it joins Cromwell Road. It is hard to see in the morning when it is dark, I am surprised it hasn&amp;#39;t taken anyone off their bicycle or motorbike. It is danger and needs to be fixed quickly&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 65, Severn Road, Lynworth, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882473&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882473</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.90724 -2.05601</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree slowly toppling onto path, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882327</link>
<description>There is a rotten tree that is leaning more and more, and bringing down the hedgerow too. This makes the path narrow and is starting to restrict the height too. As this is poorly lit at night this is likely to cause injury to walkers and cyclists who might not expect to be confronted with low hanging branches.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6882327.0.jpeg?6c5d421a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 3, Hazebrouck Close, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882327&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction caused by tree</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882327</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887696 -2.113469</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Running water, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882326</link>
<description>Drain blocked or damaged, every time we have rain water running down the road for weeks, cars spraying water over our buildings continuously.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Down Hatherley Lane, Down Hatherley, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882326&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882326</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901825 -2.199912</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Numerous deep dangerous pot holes previously &#39;sort of&#39; repaired are all back. AGAIN, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882288</link>
<description>Various pot holes along butts lane from the junction with bushcombe lane all the way up the road. Previously patched but they are back (again) and will continue to return unless repaired properly, not just a bit of tarmac shoved in them. The minute there is bad weather eg rain, the tarmac comes out. This is a regular problem and might I suggest that the width of the road where there are a few potholes gets done rather than patches. I appreciate it is going to get resurfaced alledgedly in 2025/6 but you will be coming back regularly if they are just filled individually&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Butt&#39;s Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882288&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882288</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.949404 -2.043538</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Noisy and dangerous manhole cover, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882263</link>
<description>Outside 75 / 77 Church Road Leckhampton. This issue has been raised several times before by me and other neighbours but nothing has been done. The last report was apparently referred &amp;quot;to the appropriate authority&amp;quot; but nothing has happened. This issue has been going on for months now. I consider that it is necessary to continue to report this issue for the purpose of potential legal actions in the event of any damage or injuries that may occur in order that public officials may be held to account.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 75, Church Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882263&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882263</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.87586 -2.080849</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post or sign leaning slightly (less than 20 degrees) problem, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882197</link>
<description>Customer reporting that 2 signs have become a safety issue - these have previously been reported, but remain uncollected.  Both signs have become a trip hazard with pedestrians having tripped over them in the dark. One is a triangular &amp;#39;road narrowing&amp;#39; sign and the other is a larger &amp;#39;road closed&amp;#39; sign.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882197&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Post or sign leaning slightly (less than 20 degrees)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882197</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907163 -2.046506</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Damaged drain, possible collapse, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882158</link>
<description>The drain on church lane just past the cart house, at the end of the red brick barns, is blocked or possibly collapsed. The water is stagnant, smelling and has oil on the surface. The road either side is corroding.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Although this lane is only used by farm vehicles and occasional others, it is the main through fare for the village for dog walking. Not a priority, but none the less a huge problem, as we are now walking on the main road, risking ours and our dogs lives with idiotic drivers, treating it like a race track.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The issue is long standing, as it always floods during heavy rain fall, but this year is the worst I&amp;#39;ve seen it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It can&amp;#39;t be walked through, as is about 10-12 inches deep, and under foot is slippery and precarious with pot holes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brock Farm Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882158&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882158</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.911646 -2.162624</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sizeable area of tarmac missing at top of Old Bath Road near centre//white line position.., 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882141</link>
<description>Sizeable area at the top of Old Bath Road when turning into OBR from Leckhampton Road. The tarmac is missing down from the bollard near to the white line area. This causes a manoeuvre by vehicles turning into OBR to miss the unevenness meaning vehicles arecturning into the on coming traffic from OBRd. Not helped by parked vehicles on the left side on the pavement when entering OBRd who are working on houses opposite…..&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 367, Old Bath Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882141&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882141</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.873216 -2.074246</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple potholes near pedestrian crossing, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881998</link>
<description>Multiple potholes on the uphill section of the road before the pedestrian crossing. Deep and on the desire line of cyclists, forcing them out into traffic as they take evasive action. Very dangerous. This issue has been present for several months. Some patching has taken place but this is of very poor quality and has not resolved the problem.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bayshill Road, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881998&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881998</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898314 -2.081129</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>TMC - Defects -CW6 Potholes  problem, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882049</link>
<description>Pothole CW 600mm  x 600mm  x 80mm in hours 2hr Emergency &amp;#10;Stop and go TM &amp;#10;At island by shops&amp;#10;Unable to stop and mark up and photograph due to traffic volume &amp;#10;Sizes are approximate (CW6 Pothole)&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882049&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>TMC - Defects -CW6 Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6882049</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.8425135341437 -2.14942797230143</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large section of the centre of the road crumbling., 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881746</link>
<description>Before you get to Farm lane, there’s a large centre section of the road crumbling away. The only way to avoid causing damage to your vehicle is to almost drive into the hedge ! A lot of this road is breaking up in the centre &amp;amp; needs sorting&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leckhampton Lane, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881746&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881746</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.870811 -2.094272</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tarmac all washed away from a round a manhole cover on Pirton lane near to Alms close, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881723</link>
<description>Near Alms close, all tarmac washed away from around a manhole cover. The road has only just had a complete resurface so what ever was used isn’t holding around the manholes in the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 207, Pirton Lane, Churchdown, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881723&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881723</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.880475 -2.181135</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>3 large potholes, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881700</link>
<description>Opposite The Gables Cottage&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6881700.0.jpeg?24a9afb8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shipton, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881700&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881700</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.866558 -1.945163</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 large potholes near to railway bridge, only repaired a few weeks ago &amp; tarmac washed away !, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881696</link>
<description>Near to railway bridge driving down towards the secondary school. 2 large potholes that keep opening up even after a repair. Needs a proper repair !&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pirton Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881696&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881696</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878605 -2.17658</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sink hole not, 19th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881678</link>
<description>Not acPot hole it&amp;#39;s a sink hole&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6881678.0.jpeg?2ba9858a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 57, Copt Elm Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881678&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Poor repairs (reinstatement)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6881678</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883706 -2.053346</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>