<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Abandoned car in Andover Street, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015951</link>
<description>A red Toyota Yaris AF59 XCB has been parked in Andover Street for over six weeks without moving. It has an L plate on it and the MOT has expired. Please could this be investigated.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Andover Street, Tivoli, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015951&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015951</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 23:54:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890439 -2.083804</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown hedges obscuring view of traffic, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015688</link>
<description>The bushes along the footpath on Hatherley Road just beyond the Hatherley Gate and before Hatherley Court Gardens are overgrown.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A resident who has tried to cut them back reported finding drugs paraphernalia in the undergrowth.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Also, the bushes limit the view for drivers turning out of Hatherley Gate. This means that cars coming from the left, along Hatherley Road, only come into view when they are quite close to Hatherley Court Road making it dangerous when turning right onto Hatherley Road going towards Lansdown Road.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I understand that these bushes are on land that is the responsibility of CBC.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5015688.0.jpeg?920d5887&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Gate, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015688&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5015688</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 23:00:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892651 -2.093063</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flooded road / blocked drain Repeat problem, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013940</link>
<description>Recurring problem causes narrowing of road creating a dangerous junction&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5013940.0.jpeg?9b8a7706&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Glensanda Court, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013940&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013940</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 13:54:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894885 -2.078258</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement damgerous for wheelchairs, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013600</link>
<description>An elderly neighbour uses a 6 wheel wheelchair (2-2-2) to navigate the pavements of Benhall, but he fears getting round this corner. There is an exposed tree root and several raised slabs. His 4-wheeled wheelchair couldn&amp;#39;t take this corner without tipping up. His current wheelchair can do it, but it&amp;#39;s quite a hair-raising experience for a hemiplegic 80something year old.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5013600.0.jpeg?5be93c0f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 50, Farmington Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013600&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013600</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:40:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894227 -2.112801</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree started to blow over in the wind, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013411</link>
<description>With the high winds we&amp;#39;ve been having, this tree has gone over and is resting precariously against a hedge.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5013411.0.jpeg?6a6230fc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harry Yates Way, Springbank, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013411&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5013411</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 11:57:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913807 -2.121187</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large cone in road, 20th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5012280</link>
<description>A large unmarked cone has been placed on road by a house. You have to swerve to miss it, it is not lit at night and very dirty so it’s not easy to see in poor visibility. It looks like it has been placed on top of an access hatch. It is NOT safe.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tatchley Lane, Lynworth, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5012280&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5012280</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:27:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913036 -2.04862</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bins left on grassed area for over a year, 18th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5007470</link>
<description>Bins left on grassed area opposite #1 saddlers road pirton fields Churchdown these Bins have not been moved for over a year they are full of soil rubbish and water&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5007470.0.jpeg?d6e5090c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Saddler Road, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5007470&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5007470</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 19:27:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881902 -2.198432</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Flytip at the Location was set on Fire, 18th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004223</link>
<description>The location is the Old Quarry Entrance off Cleeve Common Road. A fly tip was obviously made there and set on fire somertime on Thursday / Friday last week.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please can it be cleared up together with the small amount of mess behind the wall&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5004223.0.jpeg?150ebc2d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Noverton Lane, Southam, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004223&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004223</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:54:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907453 -2.010114</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 Deep potholes on a Blind Bend on Aggs Hill, 18th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004190</link>
<description>The potholes are on a blind bend and vehicles going up and down Aggs Hill are moving to their opposite sides of the road to avoid them.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please can they be filled in.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Aggs Hill, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004190&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5004190</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:48:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899437 -2.03332</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous loose dislodged bricks overhead., 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503</link>
<description>Vandals have accessed top of property to apply graffiti. In the process old bricks were dislodged &amp;amp; fell to the ground leaving a very unsafe hole with other loose bricks about to fall. Suggest immediate attention before further falling of the remaining loose bricks fall &amp;amp; hurt someone. It is the access alley to where disabled people park their cars to walk into town. Dangerous&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5003503.0.jpeg?81444813&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): High Street, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:59:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899312 -2.072092</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Salt Bin on Aggs Hill Hit by Vehicle into Road, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975</link>
<description>The salt bin about half way up the steep part of Aggs Hill was hit by a vehicle last night - found early this morning in the middle of the road, blocking it. The sand / salt was strewn over the rod. The bin was moved off the road back to its positio. Please can it be re-positioned and filled up again.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Aggs Hill, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:14:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900013 -2.030112</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very noisy inspection hatch, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521</link>
<description>Loud bang Everytime a vehicle goes over the hatch . There are several hatches in the area, so I was unable to indentify the specific one causing the problem, but if standing at the Monson Ave/Swindon Rd junction, it shouldn’t be long before you hear it!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Monson Avenue, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 14:26:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903901 -2.075307</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly Tipping, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468</link>
<description>Fly Tipping AGAIN. This is becoming a popular spot for fly tipping, sadly.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5002468.0.jpeg?3c099dd9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Elkstone, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 13:57:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.814099 -2.058349</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No white road markings, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409</link>
<description>The road white road markings in centre of road have gone, cars coming down the hill after stump lane cross over into on coming traffics.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Churchdown Lane, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 13:34:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.859063 -2.177419</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Grass Cutting, 16th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927</link>
<description>The grass verges in this area have not been cut for over 4 weeks, under guidelines issued (below) it is supposed to be done fortnightly. I have seen some residents have cut sections themselves. This is not right as we pay for this to be done. Also on the green is a tree stump that is 600mm high and quite dangerous considering children play here, and god forbid a child falling onto it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Maintenance of grass verges Grass verges are the responsibility of Gloucestershire County Council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In Cheltenham, the verges are maintained by Ubico (the borough council&amp;#39;s contractor) under an agency agreement with the county council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The county council pay the borough council a contribution for five cuts per year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The borough council has agreed to fund an additional ten cuts per year which enables a cycle of fortnightly cuts. This means that the grass can be kept to the same standard as in our parks and open spaces.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;What residents can expect Grass verges are cut up to 15 times during the growing season usually between March and October, depending on weather conditions Cut grass should be removed from the pavement at the time the grass is cut Strimming takes place around benches, trees and other obstacles early in the growing season and then herbicide is applied around the base of trees and obstacles in April/May and again in September/October to prevent weed or grass growth Clippings will be left on the grass verge Where bulbs are planted, the grass will not be cut until the bulb foliage has died back and this is usually six to eight weeks after flowering Where wild flower planting has taken place, the grass will be left uncut for the duration of the season, normally until around late September to early October. All foliage will be removed from the site In periods of warm, wet weather grass may grow vigorously and following cutting the clippings are likely to clump and take longer to dissipate Where appropriate - and in consultation with residents - consideration will be given to promoting biodiversity with longer grass and wild flowers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Unsuitable? Get updates Share Problems nearby UPDATES Yet again the grass cutting is not happening at the frequency specified by the County and local council of every 2 weeks, over 3 weeks since last cut!!!what are we paying council tax for, and is there an issue that the contractor cannot fulfill their obligation to the people that ultimately pay their wages. Please cut the grass.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 178, Saint Paul&#39;s Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 17:23:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907911 -2.083845</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Double yellow lines barely visible, 16th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589</link>
<description>The double yellows that are on the corners of Saddlers Lane and Tivoli Walk are not very visible leading to cars parking and blocking the access to Sadlers Lane. There is a larger issue along that stretch of Tivoli Walk, too, whereby cars park on the pavement and then block access for wheelchairs and push chairs. Maybe there should be double yellow lines along the whole of one side of that street?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5000589.0.jpeg?240037d8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Saddlers Lane, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:34:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891817 -2.087413</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608</link>
<description>Deep pothole on side of road - has been here for a couple of months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4998608.0.png?e871bc23&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cowley, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.829438 -2.04668</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>5 Potholes at the junction with Suffolk Road and Montpellier Villas, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443</link>
<description>Highways workmen arrived on Thursday 14 September to fill in the potholes. As can be seen from the photos only ONE pothole has been repaired. This is contrary to the Highways Customer Service Team who sent an email this morning stating that all of the five potholes had been repaired. This is clearly incorrect.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4998443.0.jpeg?68631a0d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 22, Montpellier Villas, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 16:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891722 -2.07958</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole on SB carriageway L1 near brown &quot;Regency&quot; sign, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224</link>
<description>Deep pothole on left hand side of lane 1, near to brown &amp;quot;Regency Cheltenham&amp;quot; sign. Unable to be specific on exact location due to shock of hitting it and subsequent damage to wheel forcing us to exit motorway at junction.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): M5, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:27:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913295 -2.150457</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Falling Tree obstructing the footpath/bridleway, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392</link>
<description>This tree is very low across footpath/bridleway. It is in danger of falling completely and potentially causing injury to walkers or horse riders. I believe it has been been reported before directly to PROW department. To find it, from Brockhampton Lane end, take footpath, cross railway line, (CAREFULLY), then continue over first bridge. It is 30/40 metres from there&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4995392.0.jpeg?a72af759&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brockhampton Lane, Kingsditch, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public rights of way</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:11:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.935338 -2.093984</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>