<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Unlit caravan not moved since July, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5270127</link>
<description>There is a caravan parked opposite Reeves Field in Charlton Park Drive. It is unlit and a danger at night as that section of road is very dark. I has not moved since July and the number plate that was on it has been removed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 30, King William Drive, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5270127&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5270127</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885795 -2.064739</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light out, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269994</link>
<description>Blacksmith Lane, light opposite allotments. Front wall of The Cusphaus&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Blacksmiths Lane, Prestbury, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269994&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269994</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.912341 -2.043893</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unable to pass along pavement safely, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269763</link>
<description>The hedge alongside 20 Cowslip Meadow is now dangerously overhanging the pavement by at least 2.5 feet. I cannot get a pushchair down the pavement safely. This has been reported before but was deemed safe! A lady on her mobility scooter had to reverse back as she could not negotiate it. How can this be deemed safe.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5269763.0.jpeg?5deb59e7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Keepers Mill, Woodmancote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269763&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269763</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.942919 -2.050044</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Brockworth Bridleway 60 - path muddy beyond resurfacing, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269758</link>
<description>The recent repair works to get rid of the muddy section of the Brockworth bridleway 60 has improved the path way, and resolved much of the problems, however, muddy sections, continue further along the path, it requested that you extend the works at the very least to the junction with the unadopted pathway leading to Bamel Way on the Gloucester business Park. Without this work, the path is still inconvenient to users of route during all seasons of the year. Given its urban location of this route, there is a need to take greater consideration of the needs of all users, including those who might try to use the route using motorised scooters and the like. In determining your prioritisation of this, I would draw your attention to the fact that this is a critical piece of infrastructure to provide access to community services based on the business Park due to your inability to adopt a roots via golf course road to the business Park from the Spinners Road ecetera development at the rear of Invista&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5269758.0.jpeg?9f3ee607&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Spinners Road, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269758&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Surface is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269758</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.840082 -2.163907</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269386</link>
<description>Customer&amp;#39;s 3 year old daughter has fallen off her balance bike as she was crossing the road. Her daughters went to A&amp;amp;E and her tooth has gone through her lip and she is very shaken up. Customer has mentioned claiming but has stressed that she does not want this happening again as this  is dangerous and her daughter was lucky as it could of been worse.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269386&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269386</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907737 -2.051759</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cars and lorries pass over and make it loose/rattle this is not the first time it’s happened also with the diversion and lorries at night make a loud bang, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269225</link>
<description>House is to the side of damaged man hole it’s not been correctly repaired and now is even worse&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5269225.0.png?9866f865&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shurdington Road, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269225&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269225</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.868407 -2.111176</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole by road junction, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269114</link>
<description>Pothole outside no 93 in the middle of the road by T junction&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brookfield Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269114&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269114</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881517 -2.159563</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is a disabled parking bay out of the front out our house that we have just completed on. We have been made aware that this was out here for the previous occupier who has now passed away., 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269087</link>
<description>1. Please can this disabled parking bay be removed? 2. Please can we place our skip here on 5th December otherwise we will have to put our skip in front of another house which we do not feel is fair to our neighbours when there is space in front of our house (we just don’t want to put it on top of the disabled markings without confirmation that this is ok to do so). Thank you&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5269087.0.jpeg?3a705c5f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brandon Place, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269087&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269087</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887296 -2.082571</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole just before traffic lights, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269038</link>
<description>About 2 foot from edge, first car position at lights.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Corinium Avenue, Barnwood, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269038&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269038</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.86617 -2.198409</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Despite an attempt at rectifying it (unsure if undertaken by GCC or property owner/developer) the f/w surface is still dangerously uneven with lowspot/dropoff at rea that can cause pedestrian incident/hazard - please fully investigate what has gone on, who did it, why it hasn&#39;t worked, and resolve matter to make safe for all legal f/w users., 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268898</link>
<description>Rear of f/w adj to new fence at north (downslope) end of street on west side o/s n.1 9or at least opp n.2)&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Great Western Terrace, Alstone, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268898&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268898</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.902467 -2.08709</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Resident&#39;s slotted downpipe-to-carriageway drainage cover is partially broken/missing exposing trough wide enough to trip residents or catch heels, walking sticks, dog paws/legs, blind stick bases, etc and is a major hazard to the legitimate f/w users (not the cars that park and obscure it - almost definitely the cause of the damage. When it the legislation preventing this coming into force??!) - please liaise with property owner to rectify this hazard before GCC incur a costly personal injury claim...., 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268866</link>
<description>Vicinity of nos 28/28 (property numbers are sequential in Burton St).&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 28, Burton Street, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268866&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268866</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903185 -2.083494</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268877</link>
<description>Pothole in the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268877&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268877</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.916825 -2.119359</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269000</link>
<description>Large pothole in road needs urgent inspection - picture attached&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269000&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5269000</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.971096 -1.988253</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork problem, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268105</link>
<description>Email rcvd 29.11.23 - &amp;#10;Good Afternoon, &amp;#10;&amp;#10;I would like to report an issue with the drainage from our property. I have contacted Severn Trent who sent me to Cheltenham Borough Council who have told me it is Gloucestershire Highways domaine.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The rainwater gulley at the front of our property fills up very quickly under usual heavy rain and is slow to drain away. I have attached a photo and video of the drains after just 1 hour of extreme heavy rain in the storm we had in October. The drain backed up so badly that the driveway access to our front door was completely flooded with 2-3 inches of water at the deepest points. I had to carry my two sons over it so their school shoes didn&amp;#39;t get flooded.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once the rain stopped completely it took 2 hours to slowly runaway (Our neighbours did not have an issue like this).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This has been an issue since we first moved to the property and seems to be worsening.&amp;#10;&amp;#10; Earlier this year and we have since had gravel and channel drains installed to the front and side of our property to help the drainage issue, but it has made little difference as the issue is that our gulley flow can&amp;#39;t handle the volume of water from the downpipe coming off the roof. &amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am very concerned that this level of flooding happened after just one hour of heavy rain, I dread to think what a day of it would be like! &amp;#10;&amp;#10;I called a local drainage company out who have confirmed our property and drains are well maintained and clear from debris. They suggested that slow drainage would be the cause of the storm drain assets beyond our property. &amp;#10;&amp;#10;We have located 2 manholes at the front of neighbouring properties which we believe are likely serve our property for storm drainage. Both looked very old in the way they were built with our drainage company explaining there is likely no utility maps of them and that we would need to ask the Council for CCTV, or a dye test carried out to work out where our water goes and what issues there is along the line (cont...see attached)&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268105&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268105</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882474 -2.097643</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>This &quot;disabled&quot; parking space appeared suddenly yesterday. It is taking up two car spaces and residents here are wondering if it&#39;s legitimate. The owner of the vehicle is Rebecca Perrett, 5 Aragon House, Abbots Leys Rd, GL545QX., 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267976</link>
<description>On Abbots Leys Road. Just outside Aragon House.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5267976.0.jpeg?62a18f53&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Abbots Leys Road, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267976&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267976</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.953841 -1.973814</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268741</link>
<description>PERM&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Could you raise a perm repair enquiry for the above job LANSDOWN PARADE near play area. Original job publicly reported as possibsinkhole , from photos cant see what defect is.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;USRN 6700663&amp;#10;Pothole - Large hole in c/way, described as sinkhole, reportees car bottomed out when driven into&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268741&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5268741</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.895765 -2.089607</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stop sign too low., 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267680</link>
<description>This stop sign, where Back Lane joins the North Street, Greet Road, Gretton Road junction is, in my opinion, fixed too low on the lamppost. I am 6 ft 1inch high and every time I walk this way I have to be really careful not to crack my head on the sign.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It should be the work of moments for one of you engineers to move it up by 12 inches.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5267680.0.jpeg?dff954ae&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Back Lane, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267680&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267680</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.955669 -1.966544</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lights not changing - red in both directions, 30th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267290</link>
<description>Lights remaining red&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267290&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The traffic light has been vandalised</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5267290</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884217 -2.142519</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Continuous potholes and road surface defects along Old Bath Road between Charlton Park Drive and Pilley Bridge, 29th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266997</link>
<description>See above&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Charlton Park Drive, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266997&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266997</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886348 -2.068856</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Raised pavement in several places due to roots from tree, 29th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266471</link>
<description>I have already reported this and was advised the repair was done. I expected the tarmac to be redone but nothing has been done. On the corner of Pilley lane by the sign, the pavement is raised which is a tripping hazard. Also this continues past the road sign and into Pilley Lane.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Pilley Lane, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266471&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5266471</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.876606 -2.076673</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>