<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Burnt sofa, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417972</link>
<description>Sofa flytipped on grass next to entrance of All Saints school. Has also been set on fire. Sofa cushions are scattered down towards Welch and Howell road on the street too by the hedges and towards oak tree.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6417972.0.jpeg?bbc6b251&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Seabright Close, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417972&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417972</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:04:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913511 -2.111456</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole patch outside St Nicholas Hall, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417766</link>
<description>On hedge side of road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 78, Swindon Lane, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417766&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417766</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:05:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.9165 -2.078199</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large branch snapped off and hanging above foot path and car, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417523</link>
<description>Please can you send a team to pull down/ make safe this large snapped off branch? It&amp;#39;s on the southern end of the row of 4 Cleevemont town houses closest to #23 Cleevelands Drive.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6417523.0.jpeg?4b58aaa2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 23, Cleevelands Drive, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417523&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417523</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:14:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.914869 -2.07206</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Slightly sunken low drain cover, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417489</link>
<description>I would not class as emergency but the drain cover on the corner whilst heading west on A40 just after reservoir has definitely dropped sunken slightly and needs repairing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A40, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417489&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417489</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:08:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.874963 -2.020443</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Obstructed path following Environment Agency Flood Alleviation Scheme completed 2012, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417458</link>
<description>The planning scheme for the flood alleviation scheme submitted by the Environment Agency included proposals for the extinguishment of parts of two paths and the diversion of EHU5 and EHU3. This was granted consent by Tewkesbury Borough on 9 December 2010 under planning reference 10/00893/FUL.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;An application was also made by Tewkesbury Borough Council (10/00894/FTP) for the diversion of parts of EHU 3 and EHU5 footpaths along with the extinguishment of parts of EHU3 and EHU2A under Town and Country Planning Act 1990 powers as the changes were necessary to enable the development to take place. The proposed changes are shown in one of the photographs attached. This was supported at the time by Hucclecote Parish Council and consultation had taken place with the Gloucester Group of the Ramblers Association, details of this consultation are included in the design and access statement to the planning application.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This application is now problematic as Town and Country Planning powers to divert/extinguish routes only exist before the development is “substantially complete” and in the normal course of events resolving this problem would require a new application under Highways Act powers. Four public authorities were involved in this project – Gloucestershire County Council, Gloucester City Council, the Environment Agency and Tewkesbury Borough Council. The evidence suggests that the Environment Agency made reasonable endeavours to resolve this matter. As Tewkesbury Borough Council did not progress the rights of way application it bears a high degree of responsibility for this. I have made a formal complaint on behalf of the Open Spaces Society, asking them to make the order under Highways Act powers at their own cost. I am in correspondence with a Senior Planning Compliance Officer at TBC who is currently taking legal advice from One Legal.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6417458.0.jpeg?bbe3c2fb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gilpin Avenue, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417458&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Path/Way illegally diverted</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417458</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:01:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.868833 -2.195133</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water main burst/leak, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417450</link>
<description>Looks like water main has burst/leaking in middle of Evesham road and is making road wet and draining down east side gutter.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Evesham Road, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417450&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417450</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:00:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.912256 -2.069531</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Good afternoon I was wondering what was happening with the footpath closure reference as above in Abbotswood Road Brockworth EY102GH1901000029464, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417339</link>
<description>This has been closed for several weeks, the problem is that there really isn&amp;#39;t an issue. Moreover there is no viable alternative route as the alternative is to walk on the grass verge or in the road. I believe that closure of the footpath is a greater hazard than it is solving. It would be ridiculous to impose road traffic restrictions to accommodate this folly. I look forward to you comments.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Abbotswood Road, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417339&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417339</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:39:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.84119 -2.155789</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Excessive flyposting/advertising on Swindon road, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417325</link>
<description>Swindon Road, Cheltenham. Travelling from the retail park. When you crest the narrow/over railway bridge there are yellow advertising signs around the Swindon Road/Windyridge road junction. These are very distracting as they look like genuine highways signage. There are approx qty10 between Windridge Road and Mauds Elm roundabout. Are you able to remove them?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 373b, Swindon Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417325&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417325</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:37:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913579 -2.091599</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is a pothole in the road outside 38 Strickland Road, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417238</link>
<description>There is a pothole in the road outside 38 Strickland Road. The edges around the outside of the pothole have broken up (as can be seen in the photo) so it will very shortly get a lot worse.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6417238.0.jpeg?66a02302&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Strickland Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417238&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417238</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:17:19 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89301 -2.061526</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Double yellow lines, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417207</link>
<description>Double yellow lines are very faded/non-existant on parts of Moorend Park Road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 20, Moorend Park Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417207&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417207</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:09:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883905 -2.085404</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flickering lamp illuminating my house very annoying in front bedroom, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417198</link>
<description>Opposite 4 Shurdington Rd Leckhampton GL530JD&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6417198.0.jpeg?51b597d9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tryes Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417198&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light is flickering/intermittent</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6417198</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:07:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.88673 -2.082178</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Roadwork sign and barrier left behind from previous works, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416511</link>
<description>On the pavement outside Western Court&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Western Road, Lansdown, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416511&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction by unpermitted skip, scaffolding, building material on pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416511</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:48:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899992 -2.089007</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>When the road was resurfaced our property (30 Painswick Road) was left without a white line, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416453</link>
<description>I understand that it is possible to ask for a white line to be painted across the road where our drive is. Our neighbours have this, recently repainted following resurfacing. As a result, people think it is OK to park in a way that blocks our drive. I know that white lines have no legal force but they are persuasive. Our local councillor (Cllr Tim Harman) advises that for a small fee we can get our part of the road painted too. Can we ask that this be done and how much is the fee?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 9, Andover Road, Tivoli, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416453&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416453</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:37:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890396 -2.082493</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The sign is illegible problem, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416403</link>
<description>Damaged Road Sign - Metre high, yellow background with a blue circle and a left arrow inside it. &amp;#10;It Is at an 45 degree angle. the sign its self is NOT damage its the holding bolts have come loose which is causing it to lean  &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416403&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The sign is illegible</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416403</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:08:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89386 -2.091652</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles problem, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416053</link>
<description>29/08/24 email rcvd ::: Hello&amp;#10;&amp;#10;While Manor Road is closed to traffic, congestion in the Kingsditch area has become close to gridlock at some times of day.  The main access to the Gallagher retail park and the Sainsbury&amp;#39;s supermarket there is via the filters at the traffic lights at Hayden Lane.  Very long queues are developing for these filters, and the length of those phases clearly need to be increased to ease the impact on an already badly congested area.  Can you please look at making this change asap, as it seems unlikely that the roadworks will be completed in the foreseeably future.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thanks&amp;#10;&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416053&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6416053</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:01:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.916203 -2.103938</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge) problem, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415795</link>
<description>Letter to be sent &amp;#39;Objects on the Highway&amp;#39; to remove large rocks placed on the verge. &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415795&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415795</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:58:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.930893 -2.055728</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The sign is illegible problem, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415794</link>
<description>email rcvd 30.08.24 - Duke Street thankfully became one-way during the Zone 15 introduction, but I’ve had concerns raised by residents as quite a few vehicles are still using Duke Street the wrong way round (entering via Princes Street) – which is obviously dangerous for pedestrians, children etc who will not be expecting a car coming from the wrong direction.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The existing no-entry signs can be quite hard to see for drivers on Princes Street, as tucked behind the wall and fairly small. While you’re working on the Princes Street resurfacing anyway, can these Duke Street no-entry signs be addressed to make more obvious?&amp;#10;&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415794&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The sign is illegible</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415794</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:32:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897816 -2.063261</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 30th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415634</link>
<description>Email received 29/08/2024 - copy attached. Customer reports that a tree is lying across the River Chelt alongside the location, having been blown down in the high winds earlier this week. They are concerned that the remaining standing tree may fall into the garden of 32 Castlefields Avenue, GL52 6YR damaging the green house.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415634&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6415634</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:08:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885258 -2.043171</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gate chained and locked to exit field on public right of way, 29th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414647</link>
<description>If travelling by road, take the turning towards Tredington from the Odessa pub on the A38. Go past Southend farm to your left. The gate to the next field on the left is chained and locked, preventing ease of access to the public right of way. The issue has been present for at least a few months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6414647.0.jpeg?8991fcc8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Stoke Road, Stoke Orchard, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414647&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Gate is damaged/missing/locked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414647</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:39:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.966437 -2.147433</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street Lighting inop all along Kingsmead Road, 29th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414395</link>
<description>All along Kingsmead Road from the junction of Princess Elizabeth Way, through to the junction of Village Road, there is zero operable street lights!! They seem to have been working on and off since CityFibre had dug up the road for the first time a little while back, but have now been off for a few weeks. People having to use flash lights to walk down the road as it’s so dark. It seems to have been reported but not acted upon and it seems that Kingsmead close and Kingsmead Avenue are also suffering what has to be a linked fault. Can we get this fixed ASAP please?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6414395.0.jpeg?ba5f95d7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 23, Kingsmead Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414395&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6414395</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:12:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.911983 -2.104266</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>