<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Poor road markings, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066626</link>
<description>The road was surfaced and road markings applied today. The road markings have been applied so thin that the tarmac can be seen below. The thickness of material used is not in accordance with the British standard.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This applies to all road markings not limited to the double yellow lines.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The poor application will impact the longevity of the road markings.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5066626.0.jpeg?417cfc83&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hermitage Street, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066626&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066626</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:21:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888463 -2.079438</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog fouling in alleyway, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066521</link>
<description>Dog fouling in alleyway between Upper Park Street and London Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 136, London Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066521&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066521</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:56:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892591 -2.062702</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vehicle leaking Diesel/oil, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066421</link>
<description>Vehicle that is untaxed and used daily is leaking excessive amounts of oil/diesel onto the road. Making it hazardous for animals and children that play in the area. It is used regularly in the Cheltenham area by GrassScape company in Cheltenham &amp;quot;www.GrassScape.co.uk. Vehicle is outside the St Pauls Hub side of the walk, in the area of numbers 15,16 St Pauls Walk. Vehicle Reg: DK08 BGV, Mitsubishi Fuso supposedly in White but is painted Grey.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 20, St Paul&#39;s Walk, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066421&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066421</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.908701 -2.079478</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge) problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066541</link>
<description>THINK TWICE before clicking links or attachments. &amp;#10;Dear Sir or Madam, &amp;#10;I write as a Director of Belbec Properties Ltd, the owners of Homelands Commercial Centre, which is situated along the side of Gotherington Lane, Bishops Cleeve, GL52 8PX.&amp;#10;As I am sure you are aware, at present major highway works are being carried out to Gotherington Lane, which we believe to include resurfacing, kerbing etc.  Unfortunately, during these works substantial damage has been caused to our planting works, which were completed as part of our planning approval (20/00089/FUL Phase 1B East Site).  It was a planning requirement that a hedge was to be re-introduced along the roadside grass verge and this work was carried out last autumn, which was the earliest we could obtain the correct plants.  This is as per the attached photo (‘gotherington planting.jpg’) and invoice, from our contractor.  As far as we were aware the plants were becoming established, and our obligations had been met.  &amp;#10;Unfortunately, during a visit to the area last week, it became apparent that your contractors have almost entirely destroyed most of this planting, whilst carrying out the works.  It would seem as though there has been little or no regard for the plants at all, which is obviously a huge waste of our time and money, as well as disappointing environmentally.  Please see the pictures and video attached.  &amp;#10;This damage has been caused through no fault of our own, and therefore we are looking to you, or your contractors, to rectify this situation.  I look forward to hearing from you at your earliest convenience, as to how this can done.  &amp;#10;Yours Faithfully&amp;#10;Georgina Lobo&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066541&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066541</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:30:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.952668 -2.055935</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The sign is illegible problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066412</link>
<description>signage originally stated traffic calming (tractor on triangle sign) and now there is only the pole that held the sign. no sign is now causing a situation of vehicles dangerously stopping to try and locate turning. breaking hard.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066412&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The sign is illegible</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066412</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:22:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.824818 -2.03783</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>General road marking and stud issues problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066261</link>
<description>Drivers constantly park on the white road markings on the bend and the yellow zigzags outside of the school.  Is there a way to make the road markings more prominent and perhaps some road signs?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066261&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road marking and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5066261</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 14:58:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.827075 -2.106037</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065681</link>
<description>Hi,&amp;#10;There was a fatal road traffic collision on the A4019, Tewkesbury Road, Cheltenham, at the junction with Brook Road (the KFC side of the road). It took place last night (03/10/23) at about 1943 hours. I am trying to see if you would be able to conduct a sequence check on the traffic lights at the junction, please? We would need to send an officer to witness the checks taking place. Obviously, this is something that we would like to get arranged and carried out as soon as possible. Please could you let me know if and when this could be carried out? I am hoping that it isn’t a massive task, but please let me know if it is going to cause major issues.&amp;#10;Regards,&amp;#10;Nick GIMBERT&amp;#10;PC 2880&amp;#10;Specialist Operations&amp;#10;Gloucestershire Constabulary&amp;#10;Incident 0420-031023&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065681&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065681</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:52:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.912362 -2.097169</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned Car, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065587</link>
<description>White BMW reg. FA07KKO abandoned on street.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 15, Victoria Terrace, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065587&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065587</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:40:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897531 -2.062617</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pot hole in road, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065417</link>
<description>There are temporary traffic lights to the side of pilgrove way. There is a large pothole in the middle of the road by these temporay traffic lights.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hayden Road, Springbank, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065417&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065417</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:04:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.916025 -2.122956</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065680</link>
<description>The kerb is damaged/ missing&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065680&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065680</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:45:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.911586 -2.035541</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065229</link>
<description>customer has called in and has mentioned that her son is having an big issue with regards to squirrels getting into his loft and she has spoken to the local council and they have directed her to GCC &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065229&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065229</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:13:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888717 -2.124116</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light is permanently out problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065228</link>
<description>50209718  Streetlight&amp;#10;Light is permanently out&amp;#10;&amp;#10;street lamp not working, lamp has a number 7 on it&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065228&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065228</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:05:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89297 -2.112019</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement cracking up, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064729</link>
<description>10 meter run of cracking on mirabelle Road. Opposite coop. Access via Sandlerling way. Possible subsidence. Ground uneven likely to catch bicycle wheels and is a trip hazard.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5064729.0.jpeg?de808f7e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Mirabelle Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064729&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064729</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:01:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.953558 -2.055327</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Obstruction caused by wall/building problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064725</link>
<description>Dear Sirs, &amp;#10; &amp;#10;Please see attached, a Form 1 Section 130A Highways Act Notice with annexures served on behalf of our client, Janet Whitehead.  &amp;#10; &amp;#10;Yours faithfully, &amp;#10; &amp;#10;&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064725&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction caused by wall/building</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064725</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:50:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.916795 -2.205629</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The sign is illegible problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065079</link>
<description>Non-Illuminated bollards and signs&amp;#10;SignThe sign is illegible&amp;#10;Sign&amp;#10;When coming from Cheltenham the road is restricted to temp 30mph limit, signs at the entry to the road at Golden valley roundabout. if you are travelling from Churchdown the speed limit sign at the M5 over bridge is showing roadworks end and a 50 mph speed limit towards Cheltenham, thus showing 2 different speed limits on the same stretch of road. I also noticed this yesterday as well. As there are speed cameras in operation on this road it will lead to people being prosecuted due to wrong signage.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065079&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The sign is illegible</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065079</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:38:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.8963 -2.137004</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in pavement problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065983</link>
<description>to be inspected by the Safety Inspector please following the receipt of the below enquiry&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065983&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5065983</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:05:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.8778 -2.048333</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064381</link>
<description>Large manhole cover has dropped and its is making a loud bang, Caller has been over it in his Porche and was very noisy and is dangerous.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064381&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064381</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 09:58:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904175 -2.0764</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Path doesn&#39;t match map problem, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064231</link>
<description>Hi, &amp;#10;I am so sorry to bother you with this problem but I need to query about my responsibility to cut the hedge at the back of my garden. &amp;#10;I have a lovely hedge at the very end of my garden with a fence behind it. There is a path at the back of my fence that goes to several houses at the back of our house. Originally some of the land at the bottom of our garden and my neighbours to the right and left also sold parts of their gardens to build these houses around 30 years ago now (before we moved here in 2017) and judging by the rights of way map the path is actually split by the houses and is their individual boundary. &amp;#10;A neighbour at the back is asking that I cut the overhanging branches at the back as it’s my responsibility. My ex partner did this a few times for her as he has a family garden and forestry business and was able to bring a truck back, do our own hedge and would politely do that for her (mostly because she always cornered him) but we are no longer together and so I would have to pay to have this done. She seems understanding that it may not be my boundary when I said that but I want to know officially. &amp;#10;I understand that if it was a right of way and public path I may be responsible for cutting it but as I said, I believe their path is private and should be maintained by the individual homes at the back, much like they would have to for broken paving slabs etc. &amp;#10;I don’t want to fall out with this neighbour and hate conflict but I also don’t have the time or money to take on something that may not be my responsibility and with 2 small children and a full time job I really don’t want to take on anything else to manage.&amp;#10;I have attached two pictures from the council website. The first is the map and the below has markers to show which house we are. &amp;#10;You can see the green is my hedge and the yellow is their path. &amp;#10;Thank you so much for any advice you can give. &amp;#10;Tilly Hughes&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064231&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Path doesn&#39;t match map</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5064231</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 09:13:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901859 -2.057084</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Racist graffiti, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062667</link>
<description>Graffiti inc under bridge&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5062667.0.jpeg?b1bbb6ea&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Swindon Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062667&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062667</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:37:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906779 -2.083072</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti on wall, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062656</link>
<description>White tag&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5062656.0.jpeg?d0838649&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Popes Close, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062656&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5062656</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:34:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906176 -2.082106</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>