<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Repairs have lasted less than 24hrs - immediate site revisit required, 26th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784333</link>
<description>FixMyStreet ref: 6654383 - urgent site revisit required for depression spanning Hatherley Road near entrance to Hatherley Gate.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This was repaired just last Fri 22nd November but due to the depression, the patch repair has turned into a larger hole and now causing even more impact on our property with HGVS and double decker buses using this route. This needs to be addressed and repaired immediately. I would also appreciate someone making contact to discuss. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784333&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784333</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89278 -2.09297</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple potholes on entrance to road at 240 down the entire road from 240 to 270, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784184</link>
<description>As above. Road dreadful impacted I’m sure by heavy traffic going into new build opposite.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Innsworth Lane, Innsworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784184&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784184</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888523 -2.205599</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sort it out, oh my lord, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784017</link>
<description>How have you not sorted this road out yet, it&amp;#39;s an abomination and a disgrace to Cheltenham. I dare you to pop your car on cruise control at 30mph and try to not explode your wheels. Absolutely ludicrous&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 131, Gloucester Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784017&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6784017</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900713 -2.093914</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Recent repair has collapsed as insufficent area and depth exposed. See photographs. To mitigate matters someone has positioned a traffic cone over it., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783984</link>
<description>TARMAC pavement outside front garden to no 16 Gratton Road, Cheltenham, on the corner of Gratton Road &amp;amp; Suffolk street.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6783984.0.jpeg?687f5493&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 16, Gratton Road, Tivoli, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783984&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783984</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889002 -2.081633</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two large potholes in depression in road, which had been fixed last week but unfortunately deteriorated already. Causing damage to nearby property., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783955</link>
<description>On Hatherley Road, just past the entrance to Hatherley Gate, heading away from Lansdown, on the side of road nearest Hatherley Gate.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The pothole is linked to a depression spanning the full width of the road, where there’s an existing fill for some kind of previous roadworks.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The potholes had been fixed last week, but the patch has already deteriorated and all the tarmac has been thrown out by car tyres travelling over it. I note that the recent fix was very minimal, and I wonder if vehicles dropping into the depression create extra wear on the pothole locations - and whether a larger patch that also addresses the larger depression would help.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The original pothole had been causing a nearby house to vibrate when large vehicles bounced through it; the recent fix had temporarily alleviated the problem slightly, but it’s now in a much worse state.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Any large vehicles (including every bus on that route) drop into the depression and further into the pothole, causing very noticeable shock waves through to a neighbouring house. These are disturbing the sleep of both our two young children, as well as ourselves who both work locally, especially my wife who is a teacher.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If it’s possible to address the larger depression and smooth it out for all traffic, beyond only the pothole, we would really, really appreciate it! Please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6783955.0.jpeg?a2c0a9be&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783955&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783955</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89278 -2.09297</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Runoff from stables causing severe damage to road surface, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783793</link>
<description>Water is running off from stables on green lane below St Bartholomew&amp;#39;s Church and runs in a torrent right down green lane to the stile where some goes across fields, the rest carrying on to The Green. The high curb at the edge of the road constrains the water on the road surface where it is eroding the road. If the curb can be altered to allow the water to run off into the hedge and field it would reduce damage to the road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6783793.0.jpeg?e8ed2f08&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783793&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783793</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.871685 -2.17143</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous Manhole cover dropping suddenly, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783753</link>
<description>The manhole cover outside 160 London Road is now dropping sharply when driven over, which is especially dangerous for motorbike riders, resulting in a significant risk of a traffic accident, especially in the rain/snow.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There are schools in the area and high pedestrian traffic volumes, creating even more concern for vehicles losing control.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6783753.0.jpeg?44c12596&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 140, London Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783753&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783753</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892172 -2.06248</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Collapsed tree blocking pathway, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783701</link>
<description>Tree has blown over on 23 november 2024 and has completely blocked footpath&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, Campion Park, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783701&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783701</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878084 -2.101924</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is a sunken drain cover in the northbound carriageway. It has been previously reported in November 2023 under Web Reference: 5212149 Enquiry Number: 22034128, and again in June 2024 under reference FixMyStreet ref: 6109829. It appears to have not been fixed, or at least any repair previously made was not long lasting. Would suggest it needs digging out, the edge reinforcing, and then the drain cover being put back so that it is flush with the surface of the road. Please could this be attended to as it presents a danger/risk of damage to car tyres/suspensions or worse still for cyclists etc., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783683</link>
<description>In the northbound carriageway after the no entry evesham road junction on the right, but before Stollards Close&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A435, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783683&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783683</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.955355 -2.066374</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large potholes on Gloucester Road, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783567</link>
<description>By bus stop.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 185, Gloucester Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783567&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783567</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899504 -2.096402</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree blown down after storm Bert. In Westal Park GL51 3 BL, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783112</link>
<description>Tree is opposite number 1 Westal Park, see attached photo. It is blocking the pavement. My husband will take it down with his chainsaw but it obviously will need to be replaced.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6783112.0.jpeg?c2f1fcce&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Westal Park, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783112&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783112</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891121 -2.092702</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road sign showing closed but road now ok, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783007</link>
<description>B4364&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Gloucester Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783007&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6783007</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900492 -2.159435</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flickering, intermittent street light on pavement in front of 47 Cudnall Street, Charlton Kings, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782975</link>
<description>Flickering and intermittent street light (mostly not working at all, leaving area pitch dark) Outside 47 Cudnall Street, Charlton Kings. Several months now.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6782975.0.jpeg?a81456a2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 47, Cudnall Street, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782975&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light is flickering/intermittent</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782975</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887958 -2.053746</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerbside drain blocked, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782909</link>
<description>This drain has been blocked for more than a year now, the water flows down Bushcombe lane every time that it rains. This will inevitably freeze during periods of cold weather, causing hazards and damage to road surfaces..&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/6782909.0.jpeg?c587bf2a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bushcombe Close, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782909&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782909</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946437 -2.043451</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes &amp; almost no tarmac suface left., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782899</link>
<description>The problem, of which there are many further down the road, is directly outside my bungalow. I have reported this several times over a period of years. I have been told its NOT deep enough. It cannot go deeper as it looks like the original &amp;#39; concrete&amp;#39; type base. It is dangerous to drivers &amp;amp; pedestrians when crossing the road. I&amp;#39;ve lived here for almost 60 years &amp;amp; can only recall any repairs happening just ONCE. The road is a disgrace.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 40, Beaumont Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782899&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782899</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.909419 -2.119132</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>G239 xdg, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782744</link>
<description>G239 XDG untaxed and on road no MOT&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Swallow Crescent, Innsworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782744&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782744</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887789 -2.2063</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked private sewer is discharging onto the highway, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782688</link>
<description>O/s 139 Hucclecote Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 139, Hucclecote Road, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782688&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782688</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.851798 -2.177036</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pedestrian crossing at the Sixways junction from Ryworth Road is not making a sound when the green man appears and it makes it unsafe to cross. The crossing time for the green man is about 4 seconds which is not long enough to cross. very unsafe for Children and is leaving them confused whether it is safe to cross., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782668</link>
<description>Sixways junction at the intersection with ryeworth road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 239a, London Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782668&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Green or amber traffic light is not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782668</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887959 -2.052252</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Are there plans to instal street lighting as there is none., 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782662</link>
<description>Bryerland Road Little Witcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bryerland Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782662&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782662</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.841845 -2.141009</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The trees are now bare, and now require some branch thinning / pruning, 25th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782580</link>
<description>The length of Pittville Lawn requires some tree branch trimming. The high winds risk injury to pedestrians and damage to parked vehicles.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 10, Pittville Lawn, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782580&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/6782580</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904688 -2.069413</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>