<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Dangerous loose dislodged bricks overhead., 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503</link>
<description>Vandals have accessed top of property to apply graffiti. In the process old bricks were dislodged &amp;amp; fell to the ground leaving a very unsafe hole with other loose bricks about to fall. Suggest immediate attention before further falling of the remaining loose bricks fall &amp;amp; hurt someone. It is the access alley to where disabled people park their cars to walk into town. Dangerous&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5003503.0.jpeg?81444813&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): High Street, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5003503</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:59:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899312 -2.072092</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Salt Bin on Aggs Hill Hit by Vehicle into Road, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975</link>
<description>The salt bin about half way up the steep part of Aggs Hill was hit by a vehicle last night - found early this morning in the middle of the road, blocking it. The sand / salt was strewn over the rod. The bin was moved off the road back to its positio. Please can it be re-positioned and filled up again.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Aggs Hill, Charlton Kings, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002975</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:14:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900013 -2.030112</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very noisy inspection hatch, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521</link>
<description>Loud bang Everytime a vehicle goes over the hatch . There are several hatches in the area, so I was unable to indentify the specific one causing the problem, but if standing at the Monson Ave/Swindon Rd junction, it shouldn’t be long before you hear it!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Monson Avenue, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002521</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 14:26:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903901 -2.075307</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly Tipping, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468</link>
<description>Fly Tipping AGAIN. This is becoming a popular spot for fly tipping, sadly.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5002468.0.jpeg?3c099dd9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Elkstone, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002468</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 13:57:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.814099 -2.058349</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No white road markings, 17th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409</link>
<description>The road white road markings in centre of road have gone, cars coming down the hill after stump lane cross over into on coming traffics.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Churchdown Lane, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5002409</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 13:34:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.859063 -2.177419</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Grass Cutting, 16th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927</link>
<description>The grass verges in this area have not been cut for over 4 weeks, under guidelines issued (below) it is supposed to be done fortnightly. I have seen some residents have cut sections themselves. This is not right as we pay for this to be done. Also on the green is a tree stump that is 600mm high and quite dangerous considering children play here, and god forbid a child falling onto it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Maintenance of grass verges Grass verges are the responsibility of Gloucestershire County Council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In Cheltenham, the verges are maintained by Ubico (the borough council&amp;#39;s contractor) under an agency agreement with the county council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The county council pay the borough council a contribution for five cuts per year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The borough council has agreed to fund an additional ten cuts per year which enables a cycle of fortnightly cuts. This means that the grass can be kept to the same standard as in our parks and open spaces.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;What residents can expect Grass verges are cut up to 15 times during the growing season usually between March and October, depending on weather conditions Cut grass should be removed from the pavement at the time the grass is cut Strimming takes place around benches, trees and other obstacles early in the growing season and then herbicide is applied around the base of trees and obstacles in April/May and again in September/October to prevent weed or grass growth Clippings will be left on the grass verge Where bulbs are planted, the grass will not be cut until the bulb foliage has died back and this is usually six to eight weeks after flowering Where wild flower planting has taken place, the grass will be left uncut for the duration of the season, normally until around late September to early October. All foliage will be removed from the site In periods of warm, wet weather grass may grow vigorously and following cutting the clippings are likely to clump and take longer to dissipate Where appropriate - and in consultation with residents - consideration will be given to promoting biodiversity with longer grass and wild flowers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Unsuitable? Get updates Share Problems nearby UPDATES Yet again the grass cutting is not happening at the frequency specified by the County and local council of every 2 weeks, over 3 weeks since last cut!!!what are we paying council tax for, and is there an issue that the contractor cannot fulfill their obligation to the people that ultimately pay their wages. Please cut the grass.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 178, Saint Paul&#39;s Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000927</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 17:23:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907911 -2.083845</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Double yellow lines barely visible, 16th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589</link>
<description>The double yellows that are on the corners of Saddlers Lane and Tivoli Walk are not very visible leading to cars parking and blocking the access to Sadlers Lane. There is a larger issue along that stretch of Tivoli Walk, too, whereby cars park on the pavement and then block access for wheelchairs and push chairs. Maybe there should be double yellow lines along the whole of one side of that street?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/5000589.0.jpeg?240037d8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Saddlers Lane, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/5000589</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:34:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891817 -2.087413</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608</link>
<description>Deep pothole on side of road - has been here for a couple of months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4998608.0.png?e871bc23&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cowley, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998608</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.829438 -2.04668</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>5 Potholes at the junction with Suffolk Road and Montpellier Villas, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443</link>
<description>Highways workmen arrived on Thursday 14 September to fill in the potholes. As can be seen from the photos only ONE pothole has been repaired. This is contrary to the Highways Customer Service Team who sent an email this morning stating that all of the five potholes had been repaired. This is clearly incorrect.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4998443.0.jpeg?68631a0d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 22, Montpellier Villas, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4998443</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 16:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891722 -2.07958</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole on SB carriageway L1 near brown &quot;Regency&quot; sign, 15th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224</link>
<description>Deep pothole on left hand side of lane 1, near to brown &amp;quot;Regency Cheltenham&amp;quot; sign. Unable to be specific on exact location due to shock of hitting it and subsequent damage to wheel forcing us to exit motorway at junction.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): M5, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4996224</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:27:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913295 -2.150457</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Falling Tree obstructing the footpath/bridleway, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392</link>
<description>This tree is very low across footpath/bridleway. It is in danger of falling completely and potentially causing injury to walkers or horse riders. I believe it has been been reported before directly to PROW department. To find it, from Brockhampton Lane end, take footpath, cross railway line, (CAREFULLY), then continue over first bridge. It is 30/40 metres from there&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4995392.0.jpeg?a72af759&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brockhampton Lane, Kingsditch, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public rights of way</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4995392</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:11:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.935338 -2.093984</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Damage to grass verges, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994596</link>
<description>Following recent work by telecoms, the grass verges have been left without grass and covered in mud.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4994596.0.jpeg?1f5ed1c5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 17, Ewens Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994596&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994596</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 22:23:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893909 -2.056584</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Damage to grass verges, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994517</link>
<description>Following recent work by telecoms, the grass verges have been left without grass and covered in mud.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4994517.0.jpeg?1f5ed1c5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 17, Ewens Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994517&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4994517</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:29:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893909 -2.056584</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reported in August sign still missing, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993745</link>
<description>The 3 marker indicator come off sign Reported via Android in the Damage to Sign (NH) category anonymously at 23:31, Sunday 6 August 2023&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Sent to National Highways less than a minute later. FixMyStreet ref: 4864528.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The marker as you come off at 11a where it goes ||| || |, the 3 one has come of the post.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): M5, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993745&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damage to Sign (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993745</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.854442 -2.17864</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown vegetation, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993711</link>
<description>The vegetation is now spilling onto private property and blocking water flows. This clearing was on a maintenance schedule but has not been done for some time and the trees and vegetation are growing and blocking the flow of water off the motorway into the flow tubes&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): M5, Upton St. Leonards, Stroud&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993711&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overgrown or obscuring view (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993711</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.851858 -2.181601</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrow bramble hedge, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993100</link>
<description>There is a large overgrown hedge with brambles coming out onto the pavement causing a nuisance and injury.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pound Close, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993100&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4993100</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 11:26:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.841681 -2.159852</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Collapsed drain outside 54 Moorend Crescent, 14th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4992653</link>
<description>Drain cover on road has badly collapsed and looks dangerous. Problem located outside 54 Mooorend crescent, though due to parking situation in the road it is only visible when cars are not parked over it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4992653.0.jpeg?30e17b9e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 54, Moorend Crescent, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4992653&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4992653</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 08:34:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882811 -2.080744</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>20 potholes over 4cm in depth from Yew Tree Cottage to Butlers Farm, 13th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991755</link>
<description>These potholes have been here since April and are growing by the day&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Elkstone, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991755&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991755</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 19:53:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.82353 -2.040913</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ongoing/Worsening problem - previously reported, 13th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991248</link>
<description>This hole/drainage point has previously been reported, it has been marked with an arrow and at one stage, was cordoned off with barriers. But nothing has ever been done, Fix My Street have continually asked me if the problem has been rectified - which it hasn&amp;#39;t - and it is now worsening. It is now a genuine hazard. We, at the BID, are happy to chase up elsewhere if we can be told whose responsibility this is?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4991248.0.jpeg?07385ce6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 5, Winchcombe Street, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991248&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4991248</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 17:30:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900308 -2.072838</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 13th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4990866</link>
<description>This rubbish has been dumped recently&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/4990866.0.jpeg?8554c2dc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Fiddlers Green Lane, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4990866&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/4990866</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:15:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899089 -2.129974</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>