<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Unsafe tree on the corner of West Drive Cheltenham. GL50 4LB, 25th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183453</link>
<description>Dear Sir/Madam, I have sent this email to various departments over the past two months without getting through to the correct one, so hopefully 🤞I have now reached the correct one.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Could I please point out to you that I reported the instability of this tree to your team back in July 2020.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Possibly one of the reasons for the instability of this tree, could be a collapsed drain. My main sewer exits my property adjacent to this tree under my wall. As you will see from the photographs I have supplied, not only is my wall leaning (it has definitely moved since I last reported the tree to you), but there is also a growing dip where water now accumulates causing quite a large puddle on the footpath. This too has become larger since I reported the issue to you back in 2020. (I believe I supplied photographs to you back then as well).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If you were to trace back and look into your records, there was a large tree removed due to honey fungus more or less where you planted this replacement tree. The original tree had extremely large roots, one of which grew under my wall at this very point and chose to show itself in my lawn. I’m wondering (as it’s possibly too much of a coincidence) that this particular root damaged the waste pipe causing the pipe to fracture (I believe it is of ceramic type). Secondly as the root decayed, together with a collapsed pipe, caused subsidence to my wall. I also have subsidence in my lawn where the root used to be.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Perhaps, together with Severn Trent Water you could investigate this together. The above might well be the reason for the instability of this tree.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I stress again his tree must be removed. If we were to have another storm the ferocity we had recently, this tree would very likely be uprooted. If you look at the photograph of the base of the tree, you will observe evidence of the movement this tree&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7183453.0.jpeg?d3d788e9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): West Drive, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183453&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183453</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.909428 -2.069868</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes on roundabout, 25th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183429</link>
<description>Roundabout next to Montpellier Terrace&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lansdown Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183429&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183429</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893883 -2.087697</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole in road, 25th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183428</link>
<description>Pothole in road heading into Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lansdown Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183428&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183428</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893883 -2.087697</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sign slipping down pole to about 6 foot off the ground so is dangerous, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183174</link>
<description>Sign is outside number 36 New Barn Lane and is for the pump room and Prestbury Cemetery. Its a hazard and the horse racing event will drastically increase the number of people at risk.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 8, New Barn Lane, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183174&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign bracket is hanging/fallen off (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183174</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.915057 -2.064823</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>What on earth is going on with this bit of road and pavement?, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183158</link>
<description>I floods due to blocked or damaged drainage. Its not finished from the retarmacing that was done last year. Its a Safety Hazard. The council need to get out there with an inspector and put a plan together to sort it. I heard it was being discussed by solicitors. Its needs sorting, not discussing! Sure the repair would be better than paying solicitors?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gretton Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183158&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183158</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964499 -2.051812</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working for a while, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183113</link>
<description>S/L outside no.10 on the west side of Cleevelands Drive&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 10, Cleevelands Drive, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183113&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7183113</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913756 -2.071877</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>New deerhurst walton road sign damaged, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182972</link>
<description>New road sign has been erected too close to the highway and has been hit and bent, by a large vehicle.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Concerned that it may cause vehicle or passenger damage&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): B4213, Deerhurst, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182972&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street nameplates</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182972</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.957818 -2.177845</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Slope at end of footpath on Hunters Road to Stoke Road It has been ages since first reported, someone put fresh tarmac on it. Slope just as bad if not worse now, the road leading to footpath is full of potholes, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182811</link>
<description>Footpath is along the fence to the houses in Hunters road, the trees were cut down two years ago so the foot path could be dug and made more accessible. Someone has chucked some tarmac on it and made the slope even less accessible, can’t go there with a walking frame or a buggy. Why is taxpayers money given to cowboys . Please make good repair so us elderly can use the footpath again. And remove the plastic guards left there for a couple of years.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7182811.0.jpeg?fa555b6b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 12A,14,15,16, Hunters Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182811&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Path/Way not reinstated after ploughing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182811</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.947387 -2.067762</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole size of manhole cover, opposite the bus stop, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182791</link>
<description>Shurdington Road (travelling towards Leckhampton) close close to the pedestrian crossing, opposite the bus stop.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;An existing pothole that was filled in and repaired last Winter. The repair has since worn away and the pothole has re appeared.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7182791.0.jpeg?dea27bed&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shurdington Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182791&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182791</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879914 -2.096007</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Long tyre width potholes over a metre long, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182752</link>
<description>Have already reported this problem and received an email to inform that it had been fixed! It very clearly has not and if anything the condition has worsened since reporting it initially. As stated before it is at the Shurdington Road roundabout junction, in the right lane (on the left hand side of this lane), as if you are turning onto Up Hatherley way.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7182752.0.jpeg?b98a4e4b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shurdington Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182752&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182752</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.876708 -2.101522</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pot holes between crickley hill entrance and national star entrance, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182727</link>
<description>Between crickley hill entrance and national star entrance. Pot holes have been there for a few years and are getting bigger - cars have to stop and then wait for oncoming traffic and drive on other side of road as potholes are so large&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A436, Coberley, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182727&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182727</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.84601 -2.088955</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>This whole stretch of rd is littered with potholes, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182648</link>
<description>This is a complaint covering the whole area of this rd both sides as there are huge holes going up Leckhampton hill and before and after Ullenwood junction coming from Birdlip. I use this rd twice a day… one driver sat outside car this morning visibly upset with a burst tyre and another one this afternoon in same place with RAC helping with burst tyre. I just cannot believe you can leave this rd in this awful, dangerous condition, holes are always patched up and due to weather this weekend, they are all open again and treacherous, a situation that has been going on for months and months… the rd was shut for 1.5 months in Sept 24 why cd this road not be replaced properly then? Lives are in danger on this road and I dread my morning and eve commutes along this road everyday. Have never witnessed anything like it in 40 years of driving and it makes me feel very sad.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leckhampton Hill, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182648&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182648</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.868255 -2.07757</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large group of potholes, dangerous when driving, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182619</link>
<description>Along the bottom of Leckhampton Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7, Leckhampton Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182619&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182619</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886476 -2.080303</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street lights not working, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182594</link>
<description>No street lights are working&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 54, Kentmere Close, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182594&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182594</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889895 -2.110621</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bricks on honeybourne, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182413</link>
<description>Water and bricks lay across the honeybourne under the bridge for Malvern Road. It looks like the bridge is degrading&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Malvern Road, Alstone, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182413&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Bridge is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182413</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900189 -2.091022</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street name plate illegible, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182348</link>
<description>The street name plate for Sussex gardens on the corner as you turn into the road is completely illegible&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sussex Gardens, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182348&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street nameplates</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182348</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.851318 -2.174151</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Massive pothole, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182332</link>
<description>Left hand side of Leckhampton Hill going up out of town. Before Hartley Lane turn. Hit it in the dark at 36mph and it blew tire Immediately. Now stranded.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7182332.0.jpeg?ce79e0dd&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leckhampton Hill, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182332&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7182332</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.862451 -2.081733</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes in road as you come down the hill, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181962</link>
<description>A series of medium sized potholes on the left hand side as you descend the hill. require avoidance meaning cars cross centre line of road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harp Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181962&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181962</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899269 -2.048178</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large deep pothole in road - increasing in size, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181841</link>
<description>On Porchester Road - hundred yards from electricity substation on junction with Millbridge Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7181841.0.jpeg?65a4dc01&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Porchester Road, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181841&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181841</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.853431 -2.188579</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Several potholes that are very deep and caused damage to car, there are several so cannot avoid, 24th February</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181797</link>
<description>At the end of the road, on the corner&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Vicarage Lane, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181797&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7181797</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.848634 -2.15673</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>